

Céline Cosneau-Ampis

UX Designer

CONTACTS

c.cosneauampis@gmail.com

06.29.12.01.64

My LinkedIn

My Portfolio

Plaisir (78) - willing to relocate

SKILLS

User Research

Personas

User Journey Map & User flows

Information Architecture

Wireframing & Prototyping

User Testing

HTML5 & CSS3

TOOLS

Adobe XD Figma Balsamiq

Marvel InVision UsaHub

Zeplin Atom GitHub

EDUCATION

UX Design Certification with a Front-End Specialization

Nov 2021 | CareerFoundry.com

1000+ hours project-based course focused on UX Design process & Front-end Development.

Master 2 in Business Administration

Jan 2015 - Mar 2017 | KEDGE BS Bordeaux (FR) & Suzhou (CHINA)

ABOUT ME

UX Designer with a professional background in Non-Profit, Education and Care. Experienced in understanding people's true feelings, motivations and expectations as well as being proactive in solving problems. Skilled in creating intuitive user-centered experiences following the agile design process, and prototyping with HTML and CSS.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Freelance UX Designer

London, Bournemouth (UK) & Plaisir (FR) | Oct 2020 - Present

Created mobile and web responsive applications design projects, from idea to prototype (more to come):

My Portfolio-Website

My portfolio-website study case

I developped my own portfolio-website using Atom & GitHub, all while learning the basics of HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript.

ExpertsNow - Responsive web application

ExpertsNow study case

Following a user-centered design process, I created a responsive web application. I conducted research, created prototypes, ran user tests and worked on the visual design.

MultiLearn - Mobile application

Following a mobile-first design approach, I created a native application. I conducted research, created rapid prototypes and ran usability tests.

Home Healthcare Provider

CHCP | Morden (UK) | Nov 2019 - Sep 2020

Provided personal care to clients, made sure they were comfortable and quaranteed the maintenance of their environment.

Private English Tutor

Acadomia & Complétude | Yvelines (FR) | Aug 2018 - Mar 2019 Individually tutored 8 and 5 students (5ème to Terminale).

Coach (Youth worker)

Life Project 4 Youth | Cebu (PH) | Fev 2017 - Fev 2018

- Managed a programme gathering 15 youth coming from a disadvantaged economical environment.
- Acted as a consultant in a micro-activity developed by the Youth from the programme.
- Taught English, Computer & Communication skills to the Youth.
- Guided the Youth individually and per group towards their social and professional integration.